<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Collection on ECWUUUUU</title>
    <link>https://ecwuuuuu.com/tags/collection/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Collection on ECWUUUUU</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:56:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ecwuuuuu.com/tags/collection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cinestill 800T &amp; Expired Kodak Portra 400</title>
      <link>https://ecwuuuuu.com/photography/new-film-stock-new-insight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ecwuuuuu.com/photography/new-film-stock-new-insight/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My New Year trip to Shenzhen was another photography trip. Alongside catching up with friends on a tight schedule, testing my first roll of CineStill 800T became a side mission. I also brought along a roll of expired Kodak Portra 400 and ILFORD HP5 Plus, as they had been sitting in my fridge for quite some time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;cinestill-800t&#34;&gt;Cinestill 800T&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The film isn’t a brand-new release; I heard about its big name from lots of film photograph KOLs at least 3 years ago. This film is basically Kodak&amp;rsquo;s Vision 3 5219 (500T) movie film. A distinctive feature of movie film is it comes with a Remjet layer, a black carbon coating designed to prevent light halation. which is a layer of black carbon coating (calls remjet) on the back of the film to prevents light halation. Traditionally, the film with a remjet layer require one extra step during develop process to remove it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guangzhou, Shenzhen, Hong Kong, and Kodak Gold</title>
      <link>https://ecwuuuuu.com/photography/gz-sz-hk-and-kodak-gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 23:59:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ecwuuuuu.com/photography/gz-sz-hk-and-kodak-gold/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After completing my master’s degree following the COVID-19 outbreak, I transitioned into full-time work. Life became busy, and I gradually set aside my film camera. Recently, I purchased Kodak Gold 200 in 120 format—Kodak’s latest film—during a visit to Guangzhou (新丽照相器材商店). I had planned to capture a few moments before leaving China. I took the film along on a three-day trip to Guangzhou, Shenzhen, and Hong Kong. Eventually, I had the film developed at GZNow Lab in Guangzhou.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>500 Hours in 307</title>
      <link>https://ecwuuuuu.com/photography/500hrsin307/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 16:07:13 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ecwuuuuu.com/photography/500hrsin307/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This work is the final project of the Photography FE (Free Elective) Course. It shows how I am &amp;ldquo;living&amp;rdquo; in classroom 307 of the laboratory building.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In June 2019, about to be my senior year, I started my graduation project. Academic research requires long-term devotion, so classroom 307, as our stronghold, became where I spent the longest time in my last year of college (since COVID-19 destroyed the second semester). I spent more than 500 hours staying in that place. To study, do experiments, rest, and entertain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outside Windowsill</title>
      <link>https://ecwuuuuu.com/photography/outside-windowsill/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2020 21:30:01 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ecwuuuuu.com/photography/outside-windowsill/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The window of my room is facing west. Clear view, not blockage. A perfect place for seeing the gorgeous sunset.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can’t really remember when and why I start taking photos from the window. Maybe because of the breathtaking scenery, or just some casual shots. But the first one I can find on my Instagram is taken in March 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Haven’t thought about making it into a series or project since the beginning. But I have shot a lot of these since 2014 and I think it will be interesting to make it into a series. And this is the result, hope you enjoy it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
