<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo on ECWUUUUU</title>
    <link>https://ecwuuuuu.com/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo on ECWUUUUU</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ecwuuuuu.com/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog Theme: ecwu-theme</title>
      <link>https://ecwuuuuu.com/post/blog-theme-ecwu-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ecwuuuuu.com/post/blog-theme-ecwu-theme/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every developer who maintains a blog eventually faces the question: &lt;strong&gt;Should I use an existing theme or build my own?&lt;/strong&gt; For me, this wasn&amp;rsquo;t just about aesthetics - it was about creating the perfect reading experience for both technical tutorials and personal reflections.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After years of blogging on various platforms and using different Hugo themes, I found myself constantly wanting just one more feature, a slightly different margin, or better typography for code blocks. Rather than continuing to patch someone else&amp;rsquo;s theme, I decided to build &lt;strong&gt;ecwu-theme&lt;/strong&gt; from the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(Switched!) Switching to a new theme ... I guess</title>
      <link>https://ecwuuuuu.com/post/new-theme-for-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 16:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ecwuuuuu.com/post/new-theme-for-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This blogsite has been using &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/shawnohare/hugo-tufte&#34;&gt;hugo-tufte&lt;/a&gt; theme (with some customization) for a while. I choose the theme because I appreciate the aesthetic look of the original Tufte $\LaTeX$ template. Using a dedicated area on the right side of the page for sidenotes, supplements images, or thoughts. Diversify the layout of an article, and make the article fun to read.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A couple of months ago, under my willingness of making enhancements to the theme. And I start to do some research on how other people are doing sidenote on their blog (Like the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gwern.net/Sidenotes&#34;&gt;great article&lt;/a&gt; by Gwern Branwen). With some &amp;ldquo;deep thinking&amp;rdquo;. I start to realize. Maybe it is not a good idea to use footnotes on the Internet pages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
