<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tailwind CSS on ECWUUUUU</title><link>https://ecwuuuuu.com/tags/tailwind-css/</link><description>Recent content in Tailwind CSS on ECWUUUUU</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ecwuuuuu.com/tags/tailwind-css/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blog Theme: ecwu-theme</title><link>https://ecwuuuuu.com/post/blog-theme-ecwu-theme/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ecwuuuuu.com/post/blog-theme-ecwu-theme/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every developer who maintains a blog eventually faces the question: &lt;strong&gt;Should I use an existing theme or build my own?&lt;/strong&gt; For me, this wasn&amp;rsquo;t just about aesthetics - it was about creating the perfect reading experience for both technical tutorials and personal reflections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After years of blogging on various platforms and using different Hugo themes, I found myself constantly wanting just one more feature, a slightly different margin, or better typography for code blocks. Rather than continuing to patch someone else&amp;rsquo;s theme, I decided to build &lt;strong&gt;ecwu-theme&lt;/strong&gt; from the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>How I Rebuilt a 2018 Project in 2025</title><link>https://ecwuuuuu.com/post/revisit-uiccourse/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 14:10:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://ecwuuuuu.com/post/revisit-uiccourse/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="prelude-the-django-and-jquery-days"&gt;Prelude: The Django and jQuery Days&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2018, I was self-studying the Django web framework for a college course. To apply what I was learning, I decided to build a project to solve a real problem: our school&amp;rsquo;s course information system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All official course information was contained within a single, large PDF file. And course details contains in more individual handbooks PDF files. Finding a specific course was a time-consuming process that required extensive scrolling and text searches. I believed I could create a more efficient and user-friendly solution.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>